{
    "id": "e7e1ff4dddfa496db3a9ccf5239fcc9c",
    "title": "Can, Could Or Be Able To",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "bbf4d8df60fc4f7899c0920767caff27",
            "title": "Can, Could Or Be Able To",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "This game ……………… be played by two people.",
                    "description": "Be able to is not normally used in passive structures.",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "be able to",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many mangoes ………………. get?",
                    "description": "We do not normally use could to say that somebody managed to do something on one occasion.",
                    "answers": [
                        "could you",
                        "were you able to",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She …………… speak six languages.",
                    "description": "Be able to often has the same meaning as can.",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "is able to",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Chennai …………….. be very warm in summer.",
                    "description": "We often use ‘can’ to say what is common or typical.",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could",
                        "is able to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………. so I didn’t go in for the race.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can't have won",
                        "was not able to win",
                        "couldn't have won"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………….. the race if I tried.",
                    "description": "We can use could have + past participle to talk about hypothetical situations. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "can have won",
                        "could have won",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………… understand what you want.",
                    "description": "Be able to often has the same meaning as can.",
                    "answers": [
                        "can't",
                        "am unable to",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "One day, I ………………… afford a home and a car.",
                    "description": "Can is not grammatically possible in future tenses.",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "will can",
                        "will be able to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I might ……………….. come.",
                    "description": "Can and could are not possible after modal auxiliary verbs.",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could",
                        "be able to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "War …………….. break out any day.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could",
                        "is able to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………… I ask you something if you are not too busy?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Can",
                        "Could",
                        "Am I able to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ………………. borrow my car if you asked.",
                    "description": "In the second conditional, we use a simple past tense in the if-clause and would / could + infinitive in the main clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could",
                        "were able to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}